(Penny:)I think it's so adorable you're
making Sheldon breakfast.
(Leonard:)Well, he's having
a rough time.
(Leonard:)Amy broke his heart,
(Leonard:)the DVR cut off the last minute
of Doctor Who...
(Leonard:)that crow followed him home.
(Penny:)Aren't you worried you're making
French toast on oatmeal day?
(Leonard:)Ah, well, what's this?
A pot of oatmeal?
(Leonard:)Or, thanks to you, what
I will now call "gloatmeal."
(Penny:)Oh, I don't want credit
for that.
(Sheldon:)Oh, Dr. and Mrs. Hofstadter,
(Sheldon:)lovely to see you
this fine morning.
(Leonard:)You're in a good mood.
(Sheldon:)Yeah, I am indeed.
(Sheldon:)I have decided,
(Sheldon:)instead of wallowing
in sadness about Amy,
(Sheldon:)it is time that I find myself
a new female companion.
(Penny:)Oh. Good for you.
(Leonard:)What brought this on?
(Sheldon:)I realized something...
when Amy was in my life,
(Sheldon:)I was hyper-focused on my work
and ignored her.
(Penny:)And you don't want
(Penny:)to make the same mistake
with the next woman.
No, I need a new woman
in my life to ignore
(Sheldon:)so I can hyper-focus
on my work again.
(Leonard:)Hey, I made
French toast sticks.
(Penny:)On oatmeal day?
(Leonard:)Ah, I also made oatmeal.
Ooh,
(Sheldon:)that's a lot of carbohydrates
for a man on the prowl.
(Sheldon:)You know what?
You eat it; you're married...
(Sheldon:)it doesn't matter
what you look like.
(Penny:)Don't take advice from a man
who threw his shoe at a crow.
♪ Our whole universe
was in a hot, dense state ♪